# MOUFADIL KHALIL

#### FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



+212 655 344 903

✓ khaliloxmedia@gmail.com

Mohammedia, Morocco

khalil-mf.netlify.app

n linkedin.com/in/khalil-moufadil

### SKILLS

- React.js
- JavaScript(ES6)
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- Laravel
- Python
- Typescript
- WordPress
- UML
- GIT
- Scrum methods
- Problem solving
- Analytical skills
- Object-Oriented Programming

### PROFILE

I am a web developer who specializes in creating web applications using front-end programming languages such as React.js, Next.js, Typescript, and TailwindCss. In addition, SGBD technologies like MySQL and MongoDB, as well as backend technologies like Laravel, are used.

## **PROJECTS**

#### **CEMETERY MANAGEMENT**

Participate in the development of sections of the CEMETERY MANAGEMENT web application.

Using Next.Js, React.Js, TailwindCss, and Typescript.

Work-based on SCRUM agile methodology.

#### PERSONAL PORTFOLIO

Personal website built with React.js, styled with React-Bootstrap components. fully responsive with direct message form to E-mail **PICTURES FINDER** 

Pictures web app built with React.js, styled-components, framermotion, and react-splide, all pictures provide from a Restful API

## **EDUCATION**

#### T.S FULL-STACK

Mohammedia Institute of Applied Technology 2021 - 2023

## MECHANICAL MANUFACTURING METHODS

Mohammedia Institute of Applied Technology 2017 - 2019

## EXPERIENCES

WEB DEVELOPER, SEO Sep 2023 – Present

**KWESK Morocco** 

- Web site builder using WordPress, PHP, Html and CSS.
- Search Engine Optimization and Google analytics

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER Internship – 1month DECLOEDT

- Working under SCRUM methodology
- Develop web app using Next.js, React, TailwindCss and Typescript

FREELANCER Jan 2023 – Mar 2023

**MAROSEM** 

• PHP, MySQL and JavaScript scripts debugger